valuemd.com 2004-12-06

# USMLE Step 1, Caribbean Medical Schools, Residency Review, Foreign Med School, International

| **Statistics**  
---  
We have **18219** registered users  
The newest registered user is **rowdymon**

Our users have posted a total of **137467** articles within **26563** topics

Last Updated On: 01/30/2020   
  
| **Privacy Statement**  
---  
We at Value MD Incorporated, hereafter refer as "COMPANY" are committed to respecting your privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of personally identifiable information you share with us (any information by which you can be identified, such as name, address, and telephone number). That is why the COMPANY has established this privacy policy, so that you can understand the care with which we intend to treat your information. 

Some of our Web pages utilize "cookies" so that we can better serve you with more tailored information when you return to our site. Cookies are identifiers which a Web site can send to your browser to keep on your computer to facilitate your next visit to our site. You can set your browser to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. The information we collect and analyze is used to improve our service to you. 

To protect your privacy, we have adopted the following principles:

**INFORMATION**

We want to give you information about our privacy policy and assure you that we take reasonable steps to see that it is followed within our company. 

**CHOICE**

There are times when we may collect personal information from you. It is our intent to inform you before we do that and to tell you what we intend to do with the information. You will have the option not to provide the information, and in the future you will be able to "opt out" of certain uses of the information. If you choose not to provide the information we request, you can still visit most of the ValueMD.com Web site, but you may be unable to access certain options, offers, and services. 

**ACCURACY**

We do our best to maintain the accuracy of personal information you supply to us; we are working on tools that will allow you to review and update your information in the future. 

**SECURITY**

We will take appropriate steps to protect the information you share with us from unauthorized access or disclosure.   
  
**Announcement: BUT**  
---  
Posted: **teratos** @ Sun Nov 21, 2004 7:40 am  
SC Luton doesn't do that. You have to think about these things very critically. All the SC Luton campus is is a money making venture. I don't think...

 [Read Full ]  
  
Comments: 0 :: View Comments (Post your comment)  

| **Welcome Guest**  
---  
  
The time now is Mon Dec 06, 2004 2:33 pm

All times are GMT - 5 Hours  
  
**Who is Online**  
---  
In total there are **71** users online :: 14 Registered, 2 Hidden and 55 Guests

Registered Users: abdirahman, DC, MD, dkenneth, dr2004usa, katya, MokahBean, ol' man, opnr2k2, ResearchingGuy, sassy, skidoc42, SMU_Information, wcb22, williamrobert

 [View complete list ]  
Most users ever online was **2381** on Tue Jul 20, 2004 1:11 am  
**Tobi** is online waiting to chat with you 24/7!   
[ Login to join chat ]   
****  
**Poll**  
---  
**No poll at the moment** You must login to vote   

Specializing in International, Foreign and Caribbean Medical Schools and USMLE Step 1, 2, and 3 Prep, ValueMD provides a single source of information regarding all aspects of medical education ranging from premed through medical school, to residency and beyond.
